

## **Summary**

I am a target driven person who enjoys a challenge. I am very committed to making a success of anything I undertake. I am hardworking, ambitious, and I understand the value of teamwork. In each job I have undertaken, I have advanced quickly due to my product expertise and my ability to provide a high level of customer satisfaction. My greatest strength is in building relationships using a consultative selling approach, and closing the sale.

Work Experience				
2016-05 - Present	Business Development Manager			
	Pierce & Pierce Business Consulting Services			
	<ul> <li>Developed new strategies to capture market channel with new clients</li> <li>Brought new process to firm to improve growth using various marketing and communication strategies, branding the firm and attracting new clients</li> <li>Developed strategies for the firm by building corporate relationships with customers and industry/market leaders</li> <li>Utilized sales and marketing tools to create brand awareness in the market</li> <li>Improved business strategies based on customer feedback</li> </ul>			
2014-06 - 2016-04	Business Development Manager			
	Bicycle Technolabs Pvt Ltd			
	Managing a sales team of 8			
	Showing leadership in sales			
	Achieving sales targets, cold calling			
2012-03 - 2014-05	Business Development Manager Handshake Web Solutions  Closed new deals by negotiating contracts Improved market position and achieved financial goals Discovered new opportunities Identified new ideas by researching industry			
Education				

## 2013 Upgrame to Proto remove State Institute of Management Technology

2010

## t State University attermark

## Skills

Negotiations		
Problem Solving		
Competitive Analysis		
Target Achievement		
Resource Allocation		
Building Sales Teams		